

CONTACT ME

- 5959 Rue Hamilton, Montreal, Quebec, H4E 3C3
- mridulchopra444@gmail.com
- mridulchopra.com
- 514-704-6395

SKILLS SUMMARY

LANGUAGES

Java

DATABASES

- MS Sql
- My Sql
- Oracle

WEB DEVELOPMENT

- HTML, CSS, Javascript, Jquery
- Spring MVC

DEV TOOLS

- Git
- Docker

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Member of Golden Key International Honor Society at Concordia University
- University Position (3rd) during bachelor's degree.
- First Prize in Quadcopter workshop organized by IIT Delhi

MRIDUL CHOPRA

STUDENT

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am current a Masters student at Concordia University studying Information Systems Security. I have worked as Software Engineer for about one year. I have strong Problem-Solving skills & bring energy, patience, positivity and cultural values to the team and my working place.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

July 2020 - July 2021

Paxcom India Pvt. Ltd.

Software Engineer Trainee

Jan 2020 - June 2020

Paxcom India Pvt. Ltd

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

MEng in Information Systems Security

Concordia University | Jan 2020 - current

- GPA: 3.92
- A, A+. A- in all the courses.

B.Tech in Information Technology

Punjab Technical University | 2016 - 2020

- SGPA: 8.44
- Position holder in University results.

PUBLCIATIONS

- "Study and Analysis of various Cryptographic Techniques" in International Journal of emerging trends in Engineering and Management.
- "Analysis of various Cryptographic Techniques" in Punjab Union Science Congress.